https://www.bayleys.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Sign In
Forgot your password?
View Messages ()
View Order Status
Completed
Return Requests
Your Address Book
Wish Lists ()
About Us
Shipping Information Return PolicyPrivacy PolicyBlogLobster and Seafood RecipesSeafood and Lobster FactsThe Bait Shed RestaurantEmma's Eats
OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY
At Bayley's Lobster Pound we respect our customers and understand that you are concerned about your privacy and the use of your personal information. We recognize the need to protect and manage this data appropriately. We have created this privacy policy to explain our privacy practices so you will understand when and how personal information is collected, used, disclosed and protected with respect to our Web site located at www.bayleys.com. By using the Site, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy.
We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. If we make any material changes to our Policy, we will post a new policy on our Site. Therefore, we encourage you to check our Policy whenever you use the Site to see if it has been updated since your last visit.
INFORMATION ABOUT YOU
At the time you make a purchase we collect and store the following types of information:
Name
Mailing Address
E-mail address
Telephone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
Similar Information on gift recipients, if applicable
We need this information to provide goods and services that you request and to let you know of additional goods and services about which you might be interested. We may ask you to submit information about other people if you order a gift to be sent directly to the recipient. In such circumstances, we will ask for the recipient's name, address, telephone number and e-mail address.
Automatically Collected Information
We may automatically gather general statistical information about our Site and visitors to our Site, such as IP addresses, browsers, pages viewed, the number of visitors, the goods and services purchased, the transactions completed, etc. To do this, we use action tags and cookies provided by our Site analytics and marketing partners. Although these partners log the information coming from our Site on our behalf, we authorize how that data may or may not be used. In addition, our marketing partners use this information to better serve you with appropriate and relevant marketing offers.
In order for you to purchase items on this site, it is necessary for your browser to accept our cookie, which in this case is a harmless reference number that corresponds to your order. The number contains absolutely no information about you, your internet activities, email, or anything else. The number has meaning only to the shopping cart system, and only while you are shopping on this site.
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Internal Use of Personal Information
All contact information submitted by you is stored in our database and may be archived elsewhere. Our records are stored indefinitely, as are our archival backup copies. Access to your personal information will be limited to specific Bayley’s Lobster Pound employees. In general, we use personal information internally to serve our users and enable them to take maximum advantage of our Site. Because our goal is to provide products that best meet your needs, we evaluate your personal interactions with us in an effort to bring you the products which best suit your tastes. In addition, we use your information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout, and services.
We may use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests such as new products, services and promotions. The e-mail addresses that we collect are used by us to contact consumers.If you place a request for products or services, we use your personal information to ship your order.
Disclosure of Personal Information
When you supply us with your postal address or phone number online you may receive periodic mailings or phone calls from us. We do not share any information about you to other vendors and we do not sell mailing lists. If you would rather not receive such offers from us, just call or write to let us know at the address below.
In addition, we may contract with other companies providing credit card processing, shipping, data management, web promotional services, to perform these services. Should we opt to do so, we will confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours. We may also use personal information to resolve disputes, investigate problems, and to improve our products and services. In addition, we may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, to manage our Site and to enhance our Site based on the usage pattern data we receive.
However, we do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except (i) as may be necessary to perform internal analyses and business functions, (ii) as part of a business transfer, or (iii) when required by law or permitted to protect our rights, property, or safety. The following section describes these disclosure circumstances more fully.
* Business Functions. We may share personal information with third party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. In the event that we use third party vendors to assist us in performing these functions, the third parties may not use or disclose your personal information for any other purpose.
* Internal Analysis. We may use information about you for our own internal purposes, such as to estimate our audience size, measure aggregate traffic patterns as well as to understand demographic, customer interest, and other trends among our users. We may outsource these tasks and disclose personal information about you to third parties in aggregate, provided the use and disclosure of your personal information by these third parties is restricted to performance of such tasks.
* Business Transfers. Information about our users and the Site is one of our most important business assets. Therefore, information about our users, including personal information, will be disclosed as part of any merger or acquisition, creation of a separate business relating to the Site, sale or pledge of company assets as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company.
* Protection of Bayley’s Lobster Pound and Others. We may release personal information in the good faith belief that release is appropriate and necessary to comply with legal process or authority (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply our policies; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our rights, property, or personal safety of Bayley’s Lobster Pound, our users, our employees, or the public; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.
NETWORK AND INFORMATION SECURITY
Access to your information is controlled by strict internal procedures. We maintain policies about the proper physical security of workplaces and records. While we have taken efforts to guard your personal information, we cannot guarantee that your information may be not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others.
CHANGES TO OUR POLICY
We may revise and update this Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones. Any changes will be posted to this document so that you will always know what information we gather and how we use it. If we make any material changes to our Policy or how we handle your personal information, we will post an updated Policy on our Site and change the date of the Policy. If we are going to use any personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. We will use information in accordance with the most current privacy policy. The practices and policies in this disclosure replace all previous notices or statements with respect to the same subject matter. This policy was posted in November 2007.
ACCESS AND CONTROL OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
If you are a user of our Site, you may opt in to (or out of) receiving communications or solicitations, simply contacting us at:Bayley’s Lobster Pound, Inc.PO Box 304Scarborough, ME 04070-0304
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections or changes.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our Site, such as customer service responses and other administrative messages. If you do not want to hear from us, please e-mail us at bayleys@bayleys.com or call us at 1-800-932-6456.
CONTACTING US
If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, the privacy practices of this Site, or your dealings with Bayley’s Lobster Pound, we may be reached via e-mail at  bayleys@bayleys.com. Or, you may reach us by telephone at 1-800-932-6456.
Sign up for our newsletter
Contact Info
9 Avenue 6
Scarborough, ME 04074
United States
207-883-4571
FacebookTwitter
Shop
Shipping Information Return PolicyPrivacy PolicyBlogLobster and Seafood RecipesSeafood and Lobster FactsThe Bait Shed RestaurantEmma's Eats
Contact Us
Delivery Info
The Bait Shed Restaurant
Emma's Eats
Copyright 2020 Bayley's. All Rights Reserved.
Successful eCommerce Websites by epicFlowers.
All prices are in USD.
Sitemap
View Cart
Go To Checkout
